Have you forgotten who you serve!? You're not supposed to side with the prince!
Tu as oublié à qui tu dois ta loyauté !? Tu n'es pas censé être avec le prince !
What are you talking about…?
De quoi parlez-vous… ?
Cut the crap!
Arrête tes conneries !
Don't forget that you're the prince's enemy!
Le prince est ton ennemi, ne l'oublie pas  !
You.
Hé !
Unhand him at once.
Lâche-le !
I won't miss next time.
La prochaine fois, ça te touchera !
Shit!
Putain !
Your highness! Why are you here?
Prince… !
Loneal, are you alright?
Lonile, tout va bien ?
Go warm up by the fire,
Réchauffe-toi près du feu,
I'll find a blanket for you.
je vais chercher une couverture.
I'm his enemy?
Je suis son ennemi ?
What did he mean by that?
C'est quoi cette histoire ?
The necklace is gone!
Je n'ai plus le collier ?!
It's not here… or here… or anywhere!
Je ne le trouve pas !
The treasured necklace… I got from Alec…
C'est un cadeau précieux d'Alek…
What are you doing?!  It's dangerous!
Qu'est-ce que tu fais ?! C'est dangereux !
If something were to happen to you, I'd…
Si quelque chose t'arrivait, je…
Your highness…
Prince…
I lost the necklace you gave me…
J'ai perdu le collier que vous m'avez offert…
I'm so sorry…
Je suis vraiment désolé…
I'm not someone worthy of your affections.
Je ne mérite ps vos faveurs…
And… I must tell you something…
Et… je dois…
There's no need for you to speak!
Pas la peine de me dire quoi que ce soit.
No matter what secrets you may hold,
Peu importe ton secret,
I'll still accept you!
je ne compte pas te rejeter.
It's most unfortunate…
C'est dommage…
That the more I get to know him, the more I succumb to his charms…
Mais plus je le connais… Plus je tombe sous son charme…
Here's some medicine to help you recover.
Tiens, c'est un médicament.
Make sure to drink it all.
Bois-le.
It seems like medicine alone won't help warm you up…
Mais ça ne sera pas suffisant pour réchauffer ton corps gelé…
I can't stand not being able to help you when you really need it…
Quel dommage que je ne puisse pas t'aider quand tu en as besoin…
My body will warm up on its own…
Mon corps va se réchauffer avec le temps…
And… I feel so safe… when I'm with you.
L'important, c'est que je me sens en sécurité avec toi…
Err…
Euh…
Loneal, allow me to use my own heat to warm you…
Je veux te réchauffer avec mon corps.
So beautiful…
Tu es si beau.
D-Don't say that…
C'est…
Your highness…!
Prince…
A-Ah, no… If you do that, then…
Ne faites pas ça, je vais…
Your highness… Any more and I'll..!
Prince… C'est trop… !
I can see my mouth wasn't enough, and you're already craving more.
Ma bouche n'a pas suffi à te calmer.
It's true… Everything about you drives me wild!
Vraiment… Tout chez toi m'excite…
Give yourself to me.
Laisse-toi faire.
Your highness.
Prince…
Close your thighs.
Ferme tes cuisses.
Alec… This…
Alek… C'est…
Is too much like real sex… I'm gonna lose it…
J'ai l'impression qu'on le fait pour du vrai…
It's cute how naïve you are, even in such a situation.
Tu es excité, mais tu restes mignon.
Thinking about it, in the story…
Dans l'histoire,
didn't he save Lily and stay the night with her in a cabin…?
il sauve Lili puis pass la nuit avec elle dans une cabane…
I shouldn't be here, but…
Et dire que ce n'est pas moi qui devrais être ici…
Loneal, good morning.
Lonile, bonjour.
What a wonderful morning… with such lovely company.
Un superbe matin avec mon adorable Lonile.